[Music]
Aditya Aman Arjun and Akash were the
thickest of friends and they all
believed in The Prudent saying health is
wealth following this very adage Aditya
Aman and Arjun bought a base health
insurance policy of three lakh rupees
they also bought a super top a policy of
7 lakh rupees with a deductible of 3
lakh rupees Akash on the contrary did
not have a base policy but had availed
the super topper policy of 7 lakh rupees
with a deductible of 3 lakh rupees
Aditya was hospitalized and incurred a
medical expense of 10 lakh Rupees since
Aditya opted for a deductible of 3 lakh
rupees in his policy the base policy
covered 3 lakh rupees and the super top
up covered the remaining 7 lakh rupees
Amman was hospitalized twice an income
medical expenses of 2 lakh rupees each
time since someone had opted for a
deductible of 3 lakh rupees in his
policy the base policy covered 2 lakh
rupees for the first bill and one lakh
rupees for the second and the super top
up covered the remaining 1 lakh rupees
Arjun was also hospitalized twice he had
a bill of 6 lakh rupees and 2 lakh
rupees each since archon had opted for a
deductible of 3 lakh rupees in his
policy the base policy covered 3 lakh
rupees for the first bill and super top
up covered the remaining 3 lakh rupees
for the first bill and 2 lakh rupees for
the second bill
Akash was hospitalized and his medical
bill amounted to 5 lakh rupees since
Akash adopted for a deductible of 3 lakh
rupees in his super Top-Up policy the
super Top-Up policy covered 2 lakh
rupees for the fast bill
super top up your health insurance
policy with the right amount of
deductible to get the most out of it
with you when you need us the most
foreign
[Music]